Guide to the Foster Hall Collection Curatorial Correspondence, 1825-1981 CAM.FHCCC.2016
ULS Archives & Special Collections
Foster Hall Collection Curatorial Correspondence
1825-1981
ULS Archives & Special Collections
Lilly, Josiah Kirby, 1861-1948
Hodges, Fletcher, Jr., 1906-2006
CAM.FHCCC.2016
10 Linear Feet (2 file cabinets containing three drawers each)
The Foster Hall Collection Curatorial Correspondence consists of correspondence, financial records, requests for printed materials, and operational reports generated by the Foster Hall Collection from the 1930s until Fletcher Hodges, Jr.'s, retirement in 1982.
Scope and Content Notes
The majority of the record exists as correspondence generated or received by Fletcher Hodges, Jr., curator of the Foster Hall Collection until 1982. But other types of materials exist, including: reports in the form of manuals, inventories, schedules, guides, financial documents; publications in the form of articles, newsletters, press clippings, programs, manuscript drafts, and advertising. Occassionally photographs, legal documents and music are present in the file.
Generally records form the 1800s exists as copies, though original letters do exists (see Rowan, Thorton). In addition, records dating before 1930 tend to deal with the controversy surrounding the Foster homestead. Finally, only financial documents date past 1978.
The records deal with subjects such as furniture for the Memorial (see Beers, Carnegie Museum, Ginn and Comp.); Foster letters (see Braun, Fischer, Goodspeed's Bookshop), opinion on various topics (see Carnegie Institute, Crosman, Kerr, N.Y. Public Library, Wilt, Yount, Rowan-Trippet-Gaulet); Fosteriana (see Bouchard, Gammans, Goldsmith, Offers of, Parks, Foster Follow-Up, cohen); and the Foster family (see Baynam, Foster relatives, Klever, Rowan, Thorton). In addition, the record contains correspondence with collectors (see Dichter, Shapiron, Sherwood's); historians and biographers (see Coleman, Cooper, Gaul, Howard, Levy, Petersen); and artists (see Hancock, Muller, Russow, Vidas.) Other records regarding these subjects may be found within the Foster Hall Correspondence.
Biography
Fletcher Hodges, Jr. (August 6, 1906 – March 13, 2006) was the first curator of the Foster Hall Collection and as such was a leading American expert on the music of Stephen Collins Foster.
Hodges, an Indiana native, graduated from Harvard University. He was hired during the Great Depression by Josiah K. Lilly, Sr., owner of the Eli Lilly and Company pharmaceutical corporation, to organize the Lilly family's archive of Foster materials, which then numbered 20,000 items. When Lilly donated the archive in 1937 to the University of Pittsburgh's newly constructed Stephen Foster Memorial on the Pitt campus. Hodges moved from Indianapolis to Pittsburgh, Pennsylvania with the collection. What began for Hodges as a three-month assignment for Lilly endured as a 51-year curatorship of the Foster collection, which ended in 1982.
Access Restrictions
There are no restriction to the Foster Hall Collecton Curatorial Correspondence files.
Academic libraries -- Pennsylvania -- Pittsburgh; Composers -- United States; Music -- United States -- 20th century; Music -- Performance -- New York (State) -- New York; Music -- Pennsylvania -- Pittsburgh; Correspondence; Lilly, Josiah Kirby, 1861-1948; University of Pittsburgh. Foster Hall Collection; Foster family; Foster, Stephen Collins, 1826-1864
- 86:1
  - Operational Reports, 1936-1977; I.
    Scope and Content Notes
    This series consists of operational reports for the Stephen Foster Memorial and Foster Hall Collection.
    - Foster memorial Committee Minutes, 1937-1941 (File-cabinet 1, Drawer 1, Folder 1)
    - Annual Reports, Foster memorial Program, 1941-1967 (File-cabinet 1, Drawer 1, Folder 2)
    - Annual Reports, University of Pittsburgh, 1936-1940 (File-cabinet 1, Drawer 1, Folder 3)
    - Annual Reports, University of Pittsburgh, 1941-1947 (File-cabinet 1, Drawer 1, Folder 4)
    - Annual reports, University of Pittsburgh, 1948-1955 (File-cabinet 1, Drawer 1, Folder 5)
    - University Organization Manual, 1960 (File-cabinet 1, Drawer 1, Folder 6)
    - Foster Memorial Standard Operational Procedures, 1937-1977 (File-cabinet 1, Drawer 1, Folder 7)
    - Foster Memorial Schedules, 1938- [1939-1940] - 1950 (File-cabinet 1, Drawer 1, Folder 8)
    - Property Inventories, 1939-1947 (File-cabinet 1, Drawer 1, Folder 9)
  - Printed Material, 1850-1978; II.
    This series consists of correspondence related to projects about Stephen Foster, including those generated by the collection and those from outside sources.
    - Reference Works, 1850-1852, [1934-1961], 1978; 1.
      - Guides to Foster Materials (File-cabinet 1, Drawer 1, Folder 10)
      - Early Development of Music in Pittsburgh, 1944 (File-cabinet 1, Drawer 1, Folder 11)
      - Folksong in Pittsburgh, Guides, 1950 (File-cabinet 1, Drawer 1, Folder 12)
      - Foster Genealogy, 1948 (File-cabinet 1, Drawer 1, Folder 13)
      - Foster's handwriting, 1948 (File-cabinet 1, Drawer 1, Folder 14)
      - Foster's Letters, copies, 1842-1850 (File-cabinet 1, Drawer 1, Folder 15)
      - Biographical Information, Hodges, 1961, 1978 (File-cabinet 1, Drawer 1, Folder 16)
      - Biographical Information, J.K. Lilly (File-cabinet 1, Drawer 1, Folder 17)
      - Dealers in Fosteriana (File-cabinet 1, Drawer 1, Folder 18)
      - Foster Hal Reproductions Checklist, 1934-1936 (File-cabinet 1, Drawer 1, Folder 19)
      - Foster Hall Reproductions Library List, U.S./Foreign Institutions, 1938 (File-cabinet 1, Drawer 1, Folder 20)
      - Foster Hall Reproductions Library List, U.S./Foreign Institutions (File-cabinet 1, Drawer 1, Folder 21)
      - Foster Hall Reproductions Library List, U.S./Foreign Institutions, 1954 (File-cabinet 1, Drawer 1, Folder 22)
      - Foster Hall Reproductions sent to libraries, 1941 (File-cabinet 1, Drawer 1, Folder 23)
      - Foster Hall Reproductions, Unfilled Requests, Additions, [1934] - 1936, 1938 (File-cabinet 1, Drawer 1, Folder 24)
      - Mailing Lists, 1944, 1950 (File-cabinet 1, Drawer 1, Folder 25)
      - Changes of address, 1951 (File-cabinet 1, Drawer 1, Folder 26)
    - Books and Newsletters, 1920, 1931-1946; 2.
      - Foster Hall Bulletin 1-7, 1931-1932 (File-cabinet 1, Drawer 1, Folder 27)
      - Foster Hall Bulletin, 8-12, 1933-1940 (File-cabinet 1, Drawer 1, Folder 28)
      - Foster Hall Bulletin, 13, 1941-1946 (File-cabinet 1, Drawer 1, Folder 29)
      - Foster Hall Bulletin 13, Armed Services Correspondence, 1941-1943 (File-cabinet 1, Drawer 1, Folder 30)
      - Foster Biography, Hodges' Drafts, 1940-1941 (File-cabinet 1, Drawer 1, Folder 31)
      - Chronicles of Foster's Family, Morneweck's Drafts, 1943 (File-cabinet 1, Drawer 1, Folder 32)
      - Advertising, Chronicles, May 1945 - August 1945 (File-cabinet 1, Drawer 1, Folder 33)
      - Advertising (File-cabinet 1, Drawer 1, Folder 34)
      - Book Excerpts, 1920, 1935, 1944 (File-cabinet 1, Drawer 1, Folder 35)
      - Play, Jack or the Submission (File-cabinet 1, Drawer 1, Folder 36)
    - Articles, 1864-1887, 1932-1949; 3.
      - Collier's Encyclopedia Article, 1947 (File-cabinet 1, Drawer 1, Folder 37)
      - Musical Digest Articles, 1947 (File-cabinet 1, Drawer 1, Folder 38)
      - Foster's Life, 1916, 1945, 1967 (File-cabinet 1, Drawer 1, Folder 39)
      - Foster's Melodies, 1877, 1887, 1940 (File-cabinet 1, Drawer 1, Folder 40)
      - Foster and American Music, 1864, 1879, 1932-1947 (File-cabinet 1, Drawer 1, Folder 41)
      - Foster and Cities (Pittsburgh, Bardstown), 1928, 1934, 1949 (File-cabinet 1, Drawer 1, Folder 42)
      - Foster and Negro, 1867 (File-cabinet 1, Drawer 1, Folder 43)
      - Foster and South, 1940 (File-cabinet 1, Drawer 1, Folder 44)
      - Miscellaneous (File-cabinet 1, Drawer 1, Folder 45)
      - Tributes, 1936, 1947 (File-cabinet 1, Drawer 1, Folder 46)
    - Speeches, 1941-1955, 1973-1976; 4.
      - Foster's Life, 1953, 1973, 1976 (File-cabinet 1, Drawer 2, Folder 47)
      - Foster's Melodies, 1948 (File-cabinet 1, Drawer 2, Folder 48)
      - Foster and American Music and Lifestyle, 1941, 1944, 1951 (File-cabinet 1, Drawer 2, Folder 49)
      - Foster and Cities (Pittsburgh, Cincinnati), 1949 (File-cabinet 1, Drawer 2, Folder 50)
      - Foster, William B., 1955 (File-cabinet 1, Drawer 2, Folder 51)
      - Lilly, J.K., 1949, 1978 (File-cabinet 1, Drawer 2, Folder 52)
    - Visual Presentations, 1934-1959; 5.
      - Slide Shows, 1936, 1947 (File-cabinet 1, Drawer 2, Folder 53)
      - T.V., Local, 1952 (File-cabinet 1, Drawer 2, Folder 54)
      - T.V., Ed Sullivan, 1952-1953 (File-cabinet 1, Drawer 2, Folder 55)
      - T.V., John Tasker Howard's "Singing America", 1946 (File-cabinet 1, Drawer 2, Folder 56)
      - Mascot Picture's Harmony Lane, 1934-1935 (File-cabinet 1, Drawer 2, Folder 57)
      - Mascot Picture's Harmony Lane shooting script, 1944 (File-cabinet 1, Drawer 2, Folder 58)
      - Republic Picture's I Dream of Jeanie, 1952 (File-cabinet 1, Drawer 2, Folder 59)
      - RKO Radio Pictures, Inc., 1950 (File-cabinet 1, Drawer 2, Folder 60)
      - Twentieth Century Fox, [1939]-1940, 1950-1959 (File-cabinet 1, Drawer 2, Folder 61)
      - Twentieth Centry Fox Swanee River Plagiarism Case, 1939-1944 (File-cabinet 1, Drawer 2, Folder 62)
      - Twentiety Century Fox Swanee River Plagiarism Case Legal Interrogatories, 1943 (File-cabinet 1, Drawer 2, Folder 63)
    - Radio Broadcasts, 1931-1945, 1956; 6.
      - Radio Broadcasts - Civic Club of Allegheny Co., 1931-[1932]-1933 (File-cabinet 1, Drawer 2, Folder 64)
      - Radio Broadcasts, Fletcher Hodges, Jr., 1934, 1940-1945, 1956 (File-cabinet 1, Drawer 2, Folder 65)
      - Radio Continuities, 1932-1937, 1940-1944 (File-cabinet 1, Drawer 2, Folder 66)
  - Correspondence, 1825-1978; 1939-1969; III.
    This series consists of general collection correspondence, alphabetical by correspondent's last name.
    - A-Al, 1940-1965 (File-cabinet 1, Drawer 2, Folder 67)
    - Am, 1944-1945, [1950-1959] (File-cabinet 1, Drawer 2, Folder 68)
    - American Association of Museums, 1942-1959 (File-cabinet 1, Drawer 2, Folder 69)
    - American Library Service, 1938 - [1941] - 1945, 1952 (File-cabinet 1, Drawer 2, Folder 70)
    - American Society of Composers, Authors and Publishers, 1952-1967 (File-cabinet 1, Drawer 2, Folder 71)
    - An-Ar, [1940] - 1958, 1969 (File-cabinet 1, Drawer 2, Folder 72)
    - Austen, William, 1956, 1975 (File-cabinet 1, Drawer 2, Folder 73)
    - As-Az, 1939-[1940]-1969 (File-cabinet 1, Drawer 2, Folder 74)
    - Ba, 1939-1967 (File-cabinet 1, Drawer 2, Folder 75)
    - Barnes, Foster L., 1950-1970 (File-cabinet 1, Drawer 2, Folder 76)
    - Baynam, E.G., 1946 (File-cabinet 1, Drawer 2, Folder 77)
    - Be-Bl, 1945-1967 (File-cabinet 1, Drawer 2, Folder 78)
    - Beers, H.F., [1939]-1941 (File-cabinet 1, Drawer 2, Folder 79)
    - Benefield, Ruth, 1940 (File-cabinet 1, Drawer 2, Folder 80)
    - Bishop, John, 1940-1952 (File-cabinet 1, Drawer 2, Folder 81)
    - Bo, 1940-1946, 1952-1969 (File-cabinet 1, Drawer 2, Folder 82)
    - Bouchard, John, 1939-1941 (File-cabinet 1, Drawer 2, Folder 83)
    - Br, 1938-1974 (File-cabinet 1, Drawer 2, Folder 84)
    - Braun, Frederick, 1951 (File-cabinet 1, Drawer 2, Folder 85)
    - Brown University, 1940, 1949-1950 (File-cabinet 1, Drawer 2, Folder 86)
    - Bz, 1938-1944, 1954-1966 (File-cabinet 1, Drawer 2, Folder 87)
    - Ca, 1938-1965 (File-cabinet 1, Drawer 2, Folder 88)
    - Carnegie Institute, 1945, 1948-1954, 1960 (File-cabinet 1, Drawer 2, Folder 89)
    - Carnegie Museum, 1940-1947, 1970 (File-cabinet 1, Drawer 2, Folder 90)
    - Cc-Cl, 1939-1971 (File-cabinet 1, Drawer 2, Folder 91)
    - Chatauqua Program, 1953 (File-cabinet 1, Drawer 2, Folder 92)
    - Christy Scrapbook, 1940-1941 (File-cabinet 1, Drawer 2, Folder 93)
    - Civic club of Allegheny County, 1938-1954 (File-cabinet 1, Drawer 3, Folder 94)
    - Co, 1935-1967 (File-cabinet 1, Drawer 3, Folder 95)
    - Coleman, John Winston, 1942-1945, 1949, 1954-1969 (File-cabinet 1, Drawer 3, Folder 96)
    - Colen, Arthur, [1945], 1969-1971 (File-cabinet 1, Drawer 3, Folder 97)
    - Congressional Record, 1930, 1940 (File-cabinet 1, Drawer 3, Folder 98)
    - Cooper, George, 1912-1925, 1947-1950 (File-cabinet 1, Drawer 3, Folder 99)
    - Cr-Cu, 1940-1967 (File-cabinet 1, Drawer 3, Folder 100)
    - Crosman, Henrietta, 1936-1937 (File-cabinet 1, Drawer 3, Folder 101)
    - Thomas J. Crowell, Company, 1945, 1952-1954, 1961 (File-cabinet 1, Drawer 3, Folder 102)
    - D-De, 1939-1953, 1963-1966 (File-cabinet 1, Drawer 3, Folder 103)
    - De Windt, Clara, [1938], 1940-1946 (File-cabinet 1, Drawer 3, Folder 104)
    - Di-Dz, 1939-1969 (File-cabinet 1, Drawer 3, Folder 105)
    - Dichter, Harry, 1941, 1946-1959 (File-cabinet 1, Drawer 3, Folder 106)
    - Dichter, Harry, [1960-1963] - 1972 (File-cabinet 1, Drawer 3, Folder 107)
    - Dichter-Fuld Project, 1953, 1955-1956 (File-cabinet 1, Drawer 3, Folder 108)
    - Dichter-Fuld Project, 1957 (File-cabinet 1, Drawer 3, Folder 109)
    - Dichter-Fuld Project Proof, 1957 (File-cabinet 1, Drawer 3, Folder 110)
    - E, 1945-1965 (File-cabinet 1, Drawer 3, Folder 111)
    - Earhart, Will (Mrs.), 1939, [1946-1947], 1952-1954 (File-cabinet 1, Drawer 3, Folder 112)
    - Fa-Fl, 1936-1967 (File-cabinet 1, Drawer 3, Folder 113)
    - Filson club, [1946] - 1949 (File-cabinet 1, Drawer 3, Folder 114)
    - Fischer, Charles F., 1938, 1940-1941 (File-cabinet 1, Drawer 3, Folder 115)
    - Florida Federation of Music Clubs, 1939 (File-cabinet 1, Drawer 3, Folder 116)
    - Florida State Exhibit, NY World's Fair, 1939-1940 (File-cabinet 1, Drawer 3, Folder 117)
    - Fo-Fu, 1942-1953 (File-cabinet 1, Drawer 3, Folder 118)
    - Foster Hall Follow-Up, 1934-1938 (File-cabinet 1, Drawer 3, Folder 119)
    - Foster Homestead, Penn Avenue, 1924-1940 (File-cabinet 1, Drawer 3, Folder 120)
    - Foster Homsestead, Penn Avenue, Legal Proof (File-cabinet 1, Drawer 3, Folder 121)
    - Foster Homestead, Greenfield Village, 1950-1953 (File-cabinet 1, Drawer 3, Folder 122)
    - Foster Homestead, Greenfield Village, Quaife Report, 1952 (File-cabinet 1, Drawer 3, Folder 123)
    - Foster Relatives, 1939-1960 (File-cabinet 1, Drawer 3, Folder 124)
    - Fuld, James J., 1950, 1978 (File-cabinet 1, Drawer 3, Folder 125)
    - Ga-Gi, 1947-1960 (File-cabinet 1, Drawer 3, Folder 126)
    - Gala Records, 1943-1945 (File-cabinet 1, Drawer 3, Folder 127)
    - Gammons, Herold W., [1947-1954], 1959 (File-cabinet 1, Drawer 3, Folder 128)
    - Gaul, Harvey, 1939, 1946, [1952] - 1954 (File-cabinet 1, Drawer 3, Folder 129)
    - Gennett, Harry, [1943] - 1945 (File-cabinet 1, Drawer 3, Folder 130)
    - Ginn and Company, 1949, 1956 (File-cabinet 1, Drawer 3, Folder 131)
    - Go-Gu, 1940-1946, 1952-1963 (File-cabinet 1, Drawer 3, Folder 132)
    - Goldsmith, Alfred F., 1942 (File-cabinet 1, Drawer 3, Folder 133)
    - Goodspeed's Bookshop, [1950], 1958 (File-cabinet 1, Drawer 3, Folder 134)
    - Guzman, Luis, [1939-1944], 1970 (File-cabinet 1, Drawer 3, Folder 135)
    - Haa-Hap, 1940-1969 (File-cabinet 1, Drawer 3, Folder 136)
    - Haden, Charles J., [1940], 1944-1965 (File-cabinet 1, Drawer 3, Folder 137)
    - Hall of Fame, Fletcher Hodges, Jr., 1940 (File-cabinet 1, Drawer 3, Folder 138)
    - Hall of Fame, Bertha Lyons, 1940 - [Jan-Apr 1941] (File-cabinet 1, Drawer 3, Folder 139)
    - Hall of Fame, Bertha Lyons, [May-Dec. 1941], 1943-1946 (File-cabinet 1, Drawer 4, Folder 140)
    - Hall of Fame, 1965-1970, 1975 (File-cabinet 1, Drawer 4, Folder 141)
    - Hall of Fame, Press Releases, Articles, 1935, 1940-1941 (File-cabinet 1, Drawer 4, Folder 142)
    - Hall of Fame, Speeches, 1941 (File-cabinet 1, Drawer 4, Folder 143)
    - Hall of Fame, Guest Lists, 1941 (File-cabinet 1, Drawer 4, Folder 144)
    - Hancock, Walker, 1941-1964 (File-cabinet 1, Drawer 4, Folder 145)
    - Har-Hay, [1940] - 1953 (File-cabinet 1, Drawer 4, Folder 146)
    - He, 1949-1970 (File-cabinet 1, Drawer 4, Folder 147)
    - Hi, [1947-1949], 1963-1970 (File-cabinet 1, Drawer 4, Folder 148)
    - Ho, 1938-1967 (File-cabinet 1, Drawer 4, Folder 149)
    - Hoboken, 1954 (File-cabinet 1, Drawer 4, Folder 150)
    - Hodges, Fletcher, Jr., (General), 1940-1977 (File-cabinet 1, Drawer 4, Folder 151)
    - Hodges, Fletcher Jr., Loans, Notes, Inventories, 1944-1978 (File-cabinet 1, Drawer 4, Folder 152)
    - Howard, John Tasker, 1933-1939 (File-cabinet 1, Drawer 4, Folder 153)
    - Howard, John Tasker, 1940 - [1944] - 1949 (File-cabinet 1, Drawer 4, Folder 154)
    - Howard, John Tasker, 1950 - [1953] - 1964 (File-cabinet 1, Drawer 4, Folder 155)
    - Hu, 1940-1969 (File-cabinet 1, Drawer 4, Folder 156)
    - I, 1939-1964 (File-cabinet 1, Drawer 4, Folder 157)
    - Indianapolis Photo Company, 1940-1967 (File-cabinet 1, Drawer 4, Folder 158)
    - Insurance, 1940-1963 (File-cabinet 1, Drawer 4, Folder 159)
    - International Records Agency, 1944-1963 (File-cabinet 1, Drawer 4, Folder 160)
    - J, 1939-1966 (File-cabinet 1, Drawer 4, Folder 161)
    - William G. Johnston Company, 1950-1961, 1968 (File-cabinet 1, Drawer 4, Folder 162)
    - Ka, 1939-1949, 1964-1966 (File-cabinet 1, Drawer 4, Folder 163)
    - Ke, 1935-1950, 1960-1964 (File-cabinet 1, Drawer 4, Folder 164)
    - Ki-Kl, 1938-1970 (File-cabinet 1, Drawer 4, Folder 165)
    - Kentucky Colonels, 1937-1946, 1952, 1957 (File-cabinet 1, Drawer 4, Folder 166)
    - Kerr, R. Erskine, 1942-1952 (File-cabinet 1, Drawer 4, Folder 167)
    - Kleber, Louis P., 1939-1941 (File-cabinet 1, Drawer 4, Folder 168)
    - Kn-Ku, 1938-1964 (File-cabinet 1, Drawer 4, Folder 169)
    - Knapp, F.F., 1957-1958 (File-cabinet 1, Drawer 4, Folder 170)
    - La, 1939-1974 (File-cabinet 1, Drawer 4, Folder 171)
    - Le-Li, 1940-1960, 1965 (File-cabinet 1, Drawer 4, Folder 172)
    - Levy, Lester S., 1957-1978 (File-cabinet 1, Drawer 4, Folder 173)
    - Library of Congress, 1915, 1945 (File-cabinet 1, Drawer 4, Folder 174)
    - Lilly, Eli, 1947-1949 (File-cabinet 1, Drawer 4, Folder 175)
    - Lilly, Eli, 1950-1959 (File-cabinet 1, Drawer 4, Folder 176)
    - Lilly, Eli, 1962-1974 (File-cabinet 1, Drawer 4, Folder 177)
    - Lilly Endowment, 1947-1952 (File-cabinet 2, Drawer 1, Folder 178)
    - Lilly Endowment, 1954-1959, 1968, 1974 (File-cabinet 2, Drawer 1, Folder 179)
    - Lilly, J.K., 1934, 1936-1939 (File-cabinet 2, Drawer 1, Folder 180)
    - Lilly, J.K., 1940-1942 (File-cabinet 2, Drawer 1, Folder 181)
    - Lilly, J.K., 1943-1945 (File-cabinet 2, Drawer 1, Folder 182)
    - Lilly, J.K., 1946 (File-cabinet 2, Drawer 1, Folder 183)
    - Lilly, J.K., 1947-1948 (File-cabinet 2, Drawer 1, Folder 184)
    - Lilly, J.K., Death, 1948 (File-cabinet 2, Drawer 1, Folder 185)
    - Lilly Memorial Medallion, 1949 (File-cabinet 2, Drawer 1, Folder 186)
    - Lilly, Presentation of Collection of University of Pittsburgh, 1934 (File-cabinet 2, Drawer 1, Folder 187)
    - Lincoln Memorial University, 1939, 1944-1957, 1967 (File-cabinet 2, Drawer 1, Folder 188)
    - Lo, 1939-1975 (File-cabinet 2, Drawer 1, Folder 189)
    - Lu, 1947-1957, 1962-1968 (File-cabinet 2, Drawer 1, Folder 190)
    - Luce Press Clippings, Inc., 1967 (File-cabinet 2, Drawer 1, Folder 191)
    - Luther, Frank, 1939-1944 (File-cabinet 2, Drawer 1, Folder 192)
    - Miscellaneous Lyrics (File-cabinet 2, Drawer 1, Folder 193)
    - Mac, 1939-1965 (File-cabinet 2, Drawer 1, Folder 194)
    - Mc, 1939-1966 (File-cabinet 2, Drawer 1, Folder 195)
    - McKibbon Book Production, 1944-1945 (File-cabinet 2, Drawer 1, Folder 196)
    - Me-Mi, 1939-1969 (File-cabinet 2, Drawer 1, Folder 197)
    - Memorial Programs, 1940=1943, 1949-1958, 1965 (File-cabinet 2, Drawer 1, Folder 198)
    - Metzger Play, 1939, 1942 (File-cabinet 2, Drawer 1, Folder 199)
    - Mo, 1939-1973 (File-cabinet 2, Drawer 1, Folder 200)
    - Morneweck, Evelyn Foster, 1937-1940 (File-cabinet 2, Drawer 1, Folder 201)
    - Morneweck, Evelyn Foster, 1941-1944 (File-cabinet 2, Drawer 1, Folder 202)
    - Morneweck, Evelyn Foster, 1945-1946 (File-cabinet 2, Drawer 1, Folder 203)
    - Morneweck, Evelyn Foster, 1947-1950 (File-cabinet 2, Drawer 1, Folder 204)
    - Morneweck, Evelyn Foster, 1951-1959 (File-cabinet 2, Drawer 1, Folder 205)
    - Morneweck, Evelyn Foster, 1960-1973 (File-cabinet 2, Drawer 1, Folder 206)
    - Mu, 1945-1968 (File-cabinet 2, Drawer 1, Folder 207)
    - Muller, Joseph, 1936-1937 (File-cabinet 2, Drawer 1, Folder 208)
    - Na, 1939-1976 (File-cabinet 2, Drawer 1, Folder 209)
    - National Alliance of Postal Employees, 1930-1931 (File-cabinet 2, Drawer 2, Folder 210)
    - Ne, [1939]-1969 (File-cabinet 2, Drawer 2, Folder 211)
    - New York Public Library, 1939, [1941], 1951-1964 (File-cabinet 2, Drawer 2, Folder 212)
    - Ni-Nu, 1939-1969 (File-cabinet 2, Drawer 2, Folder 213)
    - O, 1948-1969 (File-cabinet 2, Drawer 2, Folder 214)
    - Offers of Fosteriana, 1936-1937 (File-cabinet 2, Drawer 2, Folder 215)
    - Pa-Ph, 1945 - [1952] - 1975 (File-cabinet 2, Drawer 2, Folder 216)
    - Pan American Union Concert, 1934 (File-cabinet 2, Drawer 2, Folder 217)
    - Parkes, Walter C., 1951-1953 (File-cabinet 2, Drawer 2, Folder 218)
    - Pennsylvania State Museum Foster Collection (File-cabinet 2, Drawer 2, Folder 219)
    - Peterson, C. Stewart, 1946 (File-cabinet 2, Drawer 2, Folder 220)
    - Pi-Pu, 1945, 1950-1967, 1978 (File-cabinet 2, Drawer 2, Folder 221)
    - Portrait, SCF, Penn Mutal, 1941, 1947-1948 (File-cabinet 2, Drawer 2, Folder 222)
    - Portrait, SCF, Klein, Joseph, 1941, 1947 (File-cabinet 2, Drawer 2, Folder 223)
    - Portrait, SCF - Abolitionist, Spenser, 1941, 1951 (File-cabinet 2, Drawer 2, Folder 224)
    - Portrait, SCF's Parents, 1971 (File-cabinet 2, Drawer 2, Folder 225)
    - Ra-Re, 1938-1975 (File-cabinet 2, Drawer 2, Folder 226)
    - Remington Rand, 1949 - [1950] - 1953 (File-cabinet 2, Drawer 2, Folder 227)
    - Republic Bank Note Co., 1939 - [1943] - 1950 (File-cabinet 2, Drawer 2, Folder 228)
    - Ri-Roo, 1940-1967 (File-cabinet 2, Drawer 2, Folder 229)
    - Rice, Dean J., 1941, 1945, 1949 (File-cabinet 2, Drawer 2, Folder 230)
    - Rivers, Tom E., 1952, 1957, 1965-1967 (File-cabinet 2, Drawer 2, Folder 231)
    - Robbins Music Company, 1938-1942, 1945 (File-cabinet 2, Drawer 2, Folder 232)
    - Ros-Ru, 1938-1965 (File-cabinet 2, Drawer 2, Folder 233)
    - Rose, Jessie Walsh, 1929-1949 (File-cabinet 2, Drawer 2, Folder 234)
    - Rowan, John, 1825 (File-cabinet 2, Drawer 2, Folder 235)
    - Rowan-Trippet-Gauley Affair, 1948 (File-cabinet 2, Drawer 2, Folder 236)
    - Russow, M.B., 1945 (File-cabinet 2, Drawer 2, Folder 237)
    - Sa, 1940-1969 (File-cabinet 2, Drawer 2, Folder 238)
    - Sabas, Frankie, 1951 (File-cabinet 2, Drawer 2, Folder 239)
    - Sc-Se, 1940-1971 (File-cabinet 2, Drawer 2, Folder 240)
    - School Song Book (3rd Edition), 1939 (File-cabinet 2, Drawer 2, Folder 241)
    - Sg-Si, 1939-1966, 1973 (File-cabinet 2, Drawer 2, Folder 242)
    - Shapiro, Elliott, 1938, 1940 - [1946] - 1947 (File-cabinet 2, Drawer 2, Folder 243)
    - Sherwood's Inc., 1938 (File-cabinet 2, Drawer 2, Folder 244)
    - Sk-sm, 1940-1965 (File-cabinet 2, Drawer 2, Folder 245)
    - So-Sq, 1937-1965 (File-cabinet 2, Drawer 2, Folder 246)
    - St, 1939-1965 (File-cabinet 2, Drawer 2, Folder 247)
    - Steamboats, 1941-1942 (File-cabinet 2, Drawer 2, Folder 248)
    - Stephen Foster Drama Association, 1959-1969, 1971 (File-cabinet 2, Drawer 2, Folder 249)
    - Stephen Foster Music, Forgeries, 1939-1940 (File-cabinet 2, Drawer 2, Folder 250)
    - Stephen Foster Music Received, 1933 (File-cabinet 2, Drawer 2, Folder 251)
    - Stephen Foster in New Orleans, 1950 (File-cabinet 2, Drawer 2, Folder 252)